Stand by. three, two, one. Where's Abbott Larkin?
That's the question at the Stamford Hotel this morning.
The President of International Computer was in the Soviet Union last week.
He was in the Bahamas on Monday.
He was in Rome yesterday.
Why is he in Stamford today talking with James Brady, president of INT?
Is he discussing a merger?
Ok, Mike. Cut.
I don't know if we can use that.
We can use it if we catch Abbott Larkin.
Let's look for him.
Did you see Larkin? Do you have the picture?
No, I just saw the car drive away.
I didn't see Larkin. Where's he going now?
He's traveling.
Larkin told me I could ask the travel agent for his flight plans.
He said he might talk to me tomorrow.
I'm going to see the travel agent now. Good idea.
I'll meet you here in an hour.
That's what is showing. And then it connects at 4:45 ...
and gets into White Planes at 6:24 ...
Well, It's what it's showing ...
Yeah, because the next one is at 6:50 from Saginaw. That gets into Detroit at 7:35.
So it's a very similar ...
You're all set. I'll get seats
and I'll put this on your American Express ...
Well, it has to be ticketed this week.
I need to find Abbot Larkin.
He's flying somewhere today, maybe to Dallas or St.Louis on TWA.
Try ST.Louis.
All right. Well,
let me check what flights are available that are going out this afternoon.
There's a TW flight leaving LaGuardia at 3:35, arriving St.Louis at 5:25.
Is he on that flight?
I cannot tell you that. I would have to call up TWA.
Well, can we do that? Certainly can.
This is Marion at Prospect Travel. Could you display your Flight 119,
LaGuardia--ST.Louis, for Larkin, L-a-r-k-i-n, first initial A or Abbot?
You're not showing anything?
It would be later today, then.
OK, uh, would you ...
No, no, that's OK ... Would you please check, uh, Flight 361 ...
At 3:53 today? ...
Yes ... Yes, same person ... Yes ...
A.Larkin?
Right. And you show he is confirmed on 361
leaving at 3:53 from LaGuardia, arriving St.Louis at 5:43? Is he going to Dallas?
Do you show him continuing on to Dallas? ...
He is. And what --
Do you show any further reservations for him? ...
So he is, um, leaving from LaGuardia today
to St.Louis, and then continuing tomorrow from St.Louis to Dallas.
OK, thank you very much ... You're welcome. Bye.
So what's his schedule?
He is on TW Flight 361 today,
the 26th, leaving LaGuardia at 3:53, arriving St.Louis at 5:43 ...
And tomorrow he is continuing on TW Flight 551,
leaving Dallas at 11:55, and arriving -- I mean, leaving St.Louis at 11:55 and arriving Dallas at 1:45.
So he's going ot St.Louis first? He's going to St.Louis today
and Dallas tomorrow from St.Louis.
Will I get there before he does?
You are leaving on the 27th, tomorrow,
from LaGuardia on American 295 at 7:30 A.M. and arriving in Dallas at 10:08.
Great. Thank you very much. That's just exactly what I need.
You'rd terrific.
Mike, I found Larkin. He's staying in St.Louis tonight.
He's flying to Dallas in the morning.
He's leaving at 11:55 A.M.
We're leaving at 7:30 A.M.
We're arriving at 10:08.
We can interview him at the airport.
OK, Jake. But what does Steven think?
And will Maria pay for the trip?
Let's find out.
First, Abbot Larkin goes to St.Louis.
He stays overnight in St.Louis.
He leaves St.Louis tomorrow morning and arrives in Dallas at 1:45 P.M.
We leave tomorrow morning at 7:30 A.M. on an American Airline flight
and arrive in Dallas at 10:08 A.M.
We get there first and interview Larkin at the airport.
I don't understand.
What does this story mean?
Abbot Larkin has the biggest computer company in the Midwest.
James Brady has the biggest computer company in the east.
Together, they control most of the country.
They can grow in the west -- California, Nevada, Origon, and Washington.
And they also have business in Europe, Scandinavia, and South America.
It's one of the biggest mergers in the history.
I have to go to Dallas, Maria.
No, I don't like it.